[The Old Story of Yu Hong]
[Episode 17]
Fang.
Why are you doing this?
Things were going so well.
Why throw it all away?
I've been so worried about you.
Tell me.
Tell me, what did Zhou ever do to you?
Everyone else who marries
and moves to Shanghai
never wants to come back.
But why are you so... so stubborn?
Why can't you appreciate what you have?
What, are you possessed or something?
You'd better go back while you still can.
Don't wait until he changes his mind
and you can't go back.
At least think about
what's best for the child.
How much is this book?
1.5 yuan.
[Literary Fiction]
What about this one?
Isn't the price written on the back?
Bring me that one.
I want to take a look.
Which one?
The one on top.
Up there, near the edge.
What, can't you tell up from down?
Can you understand a word I'm saying?
Up top!
The very top!
[Literary Fiction]
[Psoriasis Treatment and Prevention]
"Psoriasis Treatment and..."
Are you sick or something?
Why the hell did you bring me this book?
Who are you trying to insult?
Are you trying to piss me off?
Do you know who I am?
I do.
If you're buying a book,
you're a customer.
If you're not buying one,
then get out.
Who do you think you're talking to?
What's with that attitude?
What kind of attitude is that?
What kind of riffraff
do you hire around here?
to work for you?
I'm sorry.
-Have you no shame?
-Ma'am, sorry, sorry.
You may have no shame, but I do.
All right, all right.
Don't you know
what you've done?
All right, ma'am.
-She's new here.
-You look so clean-cut,
but you're rotten to the core!
What did I do? Tell me.
You weren't ashamed to do it,
but I'm ashamed even to say it.
Tell me.
Do I really have to spell it out for you?
Say it.
You want me to say it, right?
Fine. Just you wait.
We'll see whether I say it or not.
I'll tell everyone about it!
How ridiculous.
My gloves!
Poor Fang...
She has no one to stand up for her
when things like this happen.
It's just not the same
without a man in the house.
I heard her husband
dumped her and divorced her.
He didn't even want the kid.
They say he married a local woman.
What?
I heard from Fang's neighbor
that she has someone else.
The guy is in Tiecheng.
Who is it?
Apparently,
she found herself a technician
at the boiler plant.
Why are you going to Shanghai?
Will your dad even look after you?
He doesn't care about you at all.
I'm going back to Shanghai to find my dad.
Do you really have to go find your dad?
Even if you go to him,
he won't look after you.
Just stop it.
It's all because you were fooling around
that you drove Dad away.
I don't want to stay here.
What kind of godforsaken place is this?
I'm going back to Shanghai to find my dad.
Hao Jie.
I work myself to the bone all day long.
I sew clothes for people in the morning
and stuff quilts with cotton at night.
You can't be so ungrateful.
I'm going back to Shanghai to find my dad.
Mom, look! So much yummy food!
Liu Yang.
Did you guys hear that just now?
There was a huge bang. It was so loud.
Yeah, what happened?
They say the boiler room exploded.
Did anyone get hurt?
Several people did.
Especially the technician,
Liu Weiguo.
He was covered in soot
when they brought him out.
Then he must be in bad shape.
I'm telling you...
[Emergency]
Has Liu Weiguo's family arrived?
Not yet.
Hurry up and get in touch with them.
Okay.
Fang.
In my eyes,
you're prettier than that mannequin
behind the counter.
I won't be pretty when I get old.
I might not even get to see you
when you're old.
Fang.
I'm leaving.
You should go back.
I loved you.
I've never loved anyone else.
And I never will.
[The end]
♪ Cold and warm, when can they rest? ♪
[Door and Window Workshop]
♪ Looking back, how many autumns? ♪
♪ Searched everywhere, yet lost instead ♪
Having a good day today?
How could she not be happy?
♪ Did I get it or not? ♪
We found the hand.
This Wang Liye is a prime suspect.
He's been handed over
to the criminal investigation unit.
Now Juan
can finally breathe easy.
After all that work
for over half a month,
we finally got somewhere.
All that talk of gods and ghosts—
now it's all clear.
Someone did it deliberately.
But there's no evidence
that Wang Liye did it.
That guy is so suspicious.
You can tell something's off about him.
He doesn't even have an alibi.
If you had nothing to hide,
why would you run, huh?
And the way he talked,
all trembling and jittery.
It's definitely him. No doubt about it.
Even if he did run,
why would he leave the hand in the car?
And the car was parked at a gas station.
Wasn't he afraid someone would find it?
You're pretty thorough
for a household registration officer.
I've been reading detective novels
at home lately.
Anyway, this case
isn't our problem anymore.
How could we handle a murder case?
If you... if you set your mind
to committing a crime,
you can exploit every loophole there is.
What can a beat cop like us
do about it?
Once we catch Wang Liye,
the truth will come out.
But what if Wang Liye didn't run?
What if he's dead?
[Emergency]
I'll go to them and tell them I did it.
Go home.
What did they tell you?
Just say you don't know anything.
Say I told you to do it.
They're going to call the police.
Do you want to go to prison?
The department head
has known me for years.
He won't hold it against someone
who's dying.
If you go, you're done for.
How are we going to pay for it?
Where's the passbook?
I'll figure out the rest of the money.
We'll find a way.